Vladimir Tinica

514-639-7005

vltinica@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/i n/vladimir-tinica

Portfolio

Skills

- HTML and CSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- React
- jQuery
- Github and Git Version Control Software
- Databases and SQL
- Adobe Photoshop
- CorelDraw
- 3ds Max

Languages

- English B2
- French B2
- Russian A1
- Romanian A1
- Bulgarian A1

JUNIOR FRONT END DEVELOPER

Profile

Junior Front End Web Developer specializing in front end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for different web projects. Well-versed in the following programming languages: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, React, jQuery. Proficiency with graphic tools.

Experience

Web Developer - 2016 to present

Lachine, QC

- · Creating the mockups for client's website and discussing the layout design
- Choosing the right programming languages, frameworks, libraries and editing tools
- Using the programming languages and the editing tools during the development process: HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Javascript, jQuery, React, SQL, Git and design tools like Adobe Photoshop
- Completing the tasks in given delays of each project.

Leading Hand - 2007 to present

WABTEC Global Service, Lachine, QC

- Tear-down, cleaning, assembling, and testing different mechanical, hydraulic and pneumatic valves and portions for rail brake systems.
- Training and supervising new employees.
- Following and complying with the high-quality standards, 5S and safety requirements.
- Installing small components and electrical wiring as needed.
- Completing production and quality assurance forms.
- Participating actively in team meetings and group discussions.
- Communicating with engineers to clarify details.

Web Designer - 2004 to 2006

WEB-ART, Chisinau, Moldova

- Designing and creating clean and beautiful layouts for clients' websites.
- Developing project concepts and maintaining optimal design workflow.
- Working with other employees of the company in choosing the right layout design for single or multiple pages websites for individual and corporate clients.
- Completing the tasks in given delays of each project.

Abilities

- Logical thinking
- Adaptability
- Multitasking
- Complex problem solving
- Time management

- Communication
- Enthusiasm
- Visual thinking
- Creativity
- · Team player

Education

Bachelor in Agro-environmental Engineering - 2003 Moldova State Agrarian University, Moldova

Certificates

Udemy certificate: The Complete 2022 Web Development Bootcamp

ItGid certificate: REACT.JS
ItGid certificate: Javascript 2.0

ItGid certificate: HTML for Javascript Developers